Guide to the Professor William C. Moffit Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Marching Band Shows and Materials
  - Miscellaneous
    - “File Techniques” (Box 38, Folder 82)
    - “Finale” Planning Charts (Box 38, Folder 83)
    - “Grand Finale Setups” (Box 38, Folder 84)
    - “Grand Finale” Setups and Staging Action (Box 38, Folder 85)
    - Halftime Show; “America” by Neil Diamond, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 86)
    - Home Stands I (Box 38, Folder 87)
    - Home Stands II (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Identified Zero Points (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Limited Edition Drill Design Director’s Guide; “Crown Imperial” (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Limited Edition Drill Design Director’s Guide; “I Got Rhythm” (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Limited Edition Drill Design Director’s Guide; Toreador (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Limited Edition Drill Design Director’s Guide; “What I Did For Love” (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Limited Edition Drill Design Director’s Guide; “What Kind of Fool Am I” (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Masters (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - MEI Sample; Computer Printed Formations (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Formations (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Letter Formations (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - “Mosaic Basics” (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Mosaic Design Multi-Action Charts (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Mosaic Techniques (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Mt. Morris vs. Beecher; “Oklahoma” Show, September 25, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Mt. Morris vs. Fenton; “Instrument Show”, October 9, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Mt. Morris vs. Flushing; “Graduate Show”, October 16, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Mt. Morris High School; “Panther Marching Band”; Bill Moffit, Director, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - “Multi-Action Line Movement” (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - New Rudiments; Patterns (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Otterbein Col. Shows, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - “Patriotic Ideas” (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Pattern Assignments (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Patterns Clinic; p. 1 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Patterns Clinic; p. 2 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Patterns Clinic; p. 3 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Patterns in Sequence (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - “Pop Songs”, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Pregame (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Pregame Entrance; Syracuse, September 19, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Publication Diagram Masters (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Show Planning Products (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Slant Rudiments (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Squad Basic Pattern ID’s (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Square Bass Staging (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - “St. Elmo’s Fire” (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Stacked Staging (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Staging Design Action Techniques (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Stereo Street Marching (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Step 2 Setups (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Step 4 by Pairs Charting Worksheet (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Step 4 by Pairs; Super Skinny Minnie (64) (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Stunts-Finals Big Production Finales” (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Sweep Effect Letters (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - Symmetrical Spinning Letters; Charting Worksheet (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - Spinning Letters (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - “Spiritual Show” (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - “Squad Step No. 2 and No. 4” (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - “Trolley Song” (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - Untitled (Box 39, Folder 50)
- Patterns of Motion Clinics Training Material
  This series contains material used by Moffit for clinics on training band leaders to use Patterns of Motions, a marching style featuring band members in constantly changing kaleidoscope patterns, as well as a dissertation about Patterns of Motion. This new marching band style, created by Moffit, quickly became a new trend and continues to impact contemporary marching band styles.
  - Patterns of Motion Clinics Training Material
    This sub-series contains material used by Moffit for clinics on training band leaders to use Patterns of Motions. The sub-series consists of 36 folders. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent. Folder names in quotes reflect the original folder names.
    - Patterns of Motion Worksheets (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Blank Patterns of Motion Field Planning Charts (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Filled Out Patterns of Motion Field Planning Guides (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - “Patterns of Motion, 48 Piece Band, Staging Designs and Conversions” (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - “Patterns of Motion, 96 Piece Band, Staging Designs and Conversions” (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - “Patterns of Motion, Master Planning Guide, Book 1, Concepts and Basic Patterns” (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - “Patterns of Motion, Master Planning Guide, Book 2, Concepts and Techniques of Staging Design Construction and Conversions” (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - “Patterns of Motion, Master Planning Guide, Book 3, Show Techniques Part I” (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - “Patterns of Motion, Marching Band Clinic Materials” (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - “BWC WW Intros” (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - “University of Michigan – Fourth Annual National Band Conductors Conference Workshop, July 21-26, 1952” (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - “U.S. A.” (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - “Fever Kaleidoscope” (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - “144 Piece Band Masters” (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - “160 Piece Band Masters” (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - “Programmer – Book II” (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - “48 Piece Band Masters” (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - “Marching Rudiment Warm-ups” (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - “Diagonal Techniques” (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - “Show Planning Tools” (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - “FVSU” (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - “Original Master ‘Pages’” (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - “Bill Moffit’s Spiritual Show, A Ready-to-go Half Time Show Featuring Patterns of Motion, 96 Piece Band” (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - “Spinning Letters” (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - “God Bless America, Stanton P. H. S. Band” (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - “Pattern of Motion Spinning Letters (Sample Book), Bill Moffit” (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - “On Wisconsin” (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - “‘Sound of Tomorrow—Today,’ 96 Piece Band Show” (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - “Bill Moffit’s Patterns of Motion, Flip Cards at Right Edge to See a Complete Pattern of Motion (Circle Pattern #5” (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - “Patterns of Motion, Instant Letters for 96 Piece Bands, Master Chartbook” (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - “64-Pice Band” (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - “South Rampart Street Parade” (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - “God Bless America Planning Guide” (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - “Stars and Stripes Finale” (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - “Bill Bailey Stomp” (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - “New ‘Patterns’ Basic Fundamentals” (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Pattern of Motion Publications
    This sub-series contains publication about Patterns of Motion. The sub-series consists of 2 items.
    - Dissertation by Edwin P. Arnold, "Patterns of Motion and Soundpower: Their Significance to the School Marching Band," Draft, August 1980 (Item 37)
    - Dissertation by Edwin P. Arnold, "Patterns of Motion and Soundpower: Their Significance to the School Marching Band", May 1981 (Item 38)
- Purdue Band Drill Books
  This series contains drill books for several of the years Moffit was at Purdue University. The series consists of 10 folders. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
  - “Purdue University, The ‘All-American’ Marching Band,” Part 1 of 2, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - “Purdue University, The ‘All-American’ Marching Band,” Part 2 of 2, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Drill Book, Part 1 of 2, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Drill Book, Part 2 of 2, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - “Purdue University, ‘All American Marching Band,’” Part 1 of 2, 1985-1986 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - “Purdue University, ‘All American Marching Band,’” Part 2 of 2, 1985-1986 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - “The ‘All-American’ Marching Band, Purdue University,” Part 1 of 2, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - “The ‘All-American’ Marching Band, Purdue University,” Part 2 of 2, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - “All-American Marching Band Drill Book,” Part 1 of 2, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - “All-American Marching Band Drill Book,” Part 2 of 2, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Audio Recordings
  This series contains various recordings used by Moffit and the ten recordings are arranged alphabetically.
  - Audio Cassette; Indiana Department of Commerce/Wander Indiana Radio, May 22, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Audio Cassette; Jaguar Pride (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Audio Cassettes; Stephen Melillo; “Son of the Storm”; “Storm Works”; “S-Matrix” (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Audio Cassette; The University of Georgia; Redcoat Band (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Audio Cassette; Wheaties; Bobby Whiteside Ltd.; Baseball Alt. No. 3 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Record; Ohio; The Heat of It All (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Record; Soundpower Preview Record; The Big New Sound for Marching Band (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Record; “Cougar Fight Song”; “Stand Up for America” (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Record; Cougar Brass (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - CD; “Baldwin-Wallace Fight Song” (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - DVD; “UH Band on PM Magazine” (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Ephemera
  This series contains 2 boxes of personal and work related non-manuscript material. It is arranged alphabetically.
  - “Bill Moffit” Sign (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Bell (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Box of Drafting Tools (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Bumper Sticker: “Moffit Soundpower Patterns of Motion” (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Cowboy Statue (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Lansing Lions Club Speaker; Dr. William Moffit (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Bumper Sticker: "Purdue University Bands" (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - American Flag (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Belt Buckle; Budweiser (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Belt Buckle; Coca Cola (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Belt Buckle; President Bill Moffit; TBA, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Belt Buckle; UH Cougar Brass (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Business Card; Hal Leonard Publishing; Corporation of Bill Moffit (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Desk Identification; “Bill Moffit VI District Governor 1973-1975" (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Key to City; City of Bettendorf (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Key to City; Galveston, Texas (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Key to City; Indianapolis; William H. Hudnut, III (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Key to City; New Philadelphia, Ohio; Mayor Lloyd Dinger (broken), April 6, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Pin; Indianapolis 500, May 25, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Pin; National Board (FFA Agricultural Education); three (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - University Circle Plaques; Rotary Club Lafayette, Indiana (black); Home of Purdue (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - University Circle Plaques; Rotary Club Lafayette, Indiana (gold); Home of Purdue (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - University Circle Plaques; University of Houston at Clear Lake City (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - University Circle Plaques; UH at Half-Century; Education and Commitment (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Music Books
  This series consists of published music books and is arranged alphabetically. It contains 3 boxes of material. Additional published music books can be found in Series 17, Jacksonville Community Band Materials.
  - 27 Drill band Maneuvers; 2 copies (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - 40 Golden Songs of Bacharach and David, undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - A Motown Medley, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - A New Sound in the Parade, undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Alfred’s Drum-Set Handy Guide, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - An Invitation to Band Directing, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Another Op’nin’, Another Show, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - The Arranger’s Dreambook, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Arthur Pryor; Celebrated Solos for Trombone with Piano Accompaniment, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - The Bacharach and David Fun-Way Concert Band Book, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Band Central Station; Selmer; Folders (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Band Director’s Percussion Repair Model Order Sheet (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Band Instrument Repairing Manuel, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Basic Bongo Beats (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - The Best of Billings; 1746-1800 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Bill Moffit’s Patterns for Percussion; Volume II (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Bill Moffits’ Patterns of Motion Price Guide (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Bill Moffit’s Soundpower; Patterns for Percussion; Volume I (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Block Buster Handbook, undated (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Block Specials, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Choral Arranging for Schools, Glee Clubs and Publication, 1949 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Condensed Conductor Scores for Concert Band, undated (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Contemporary Percussion Technique and Method, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Corps Style Drumming for the Intermediate Drummer, undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Custom Designed Belt Buckles Flyer (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Design for the Drum Set (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Developing Drum Breaks and Fill-Ins, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Drum Corps, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Drum Major Manuel and Big Ten Football Band Charts, undated (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - The Drummers Heritage, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Drum Warm-Ups (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - 12 Easy Precision Drills; 80 Piece Band; Piersol, Frank (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - 12 Easy Precision Drills; 64 Piece Band; Piersol, Frank (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - 12 Easy Precision Drills; 64 Piece Band; Piersol, Frank (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - 12 Easy Precision Drills; 80 Piece Band; Piersol, Frank (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Early Jazz: It’s Roots and Musical Development, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Exploring Talent and Initiative; Foster, Jimmy, August 21, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Expression in Music Books (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Field Flash, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Fingering Charts for Instrumentalists, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - First Arrangement (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Folk Sing: A Handbook for Pickers and Singers, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Fun(d) Raisine Band Book, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Fundamental Method for Timpani (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Fundamental Method for Timpani (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - G. Leblanc Corps Materials (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - G. Schirmer’s Secular Choral Music, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Getting Results with School Bands, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Getzen Company, Inc, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Glenn Miller’s Method for Orchestral Arranging (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Herb Alpert and the Tijuana Brass; No. 3a, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - High School Harmony; Part I (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Hoosier Pride, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - How to Play 6/8 March Rhythms, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - How to Play Bongo Drums, undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - 1982 National/International Music Festivals (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - The Instrumentalist, 1989-2004 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - John Philip Sousa: A Descriptive Catalog of His Works, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Journal of Band Research; Vol. 25, No. 2; Vol. 26, No. 2, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Journal of Band Research; Vol. 30-31, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Journal of Band Research; Vol. 31, No. 2 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Journal of Band Research; Vol. 33, No. 1, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Journal of Band Research; Vol. 33, No. 2, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Journal of Band Research; Vol. 34, No. 1, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Journal of Band Research; Vol. 35, No. 1 and 2, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Journal of Band Research, 2000-2005 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - The Jerome Kern Songbook, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Leedy and Ludwig Drums: Bandmasters Let’s Check Your Drum Section (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Let’s All Play Bongos (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Let’s All Play Congas (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Let’s Go!, undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Let’s March on the Field, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Ludwig Drummer, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Ludwig Drummer; Vol. 8; No. 1 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Marching Band and Baton Twirling Handbook; 1-3 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - The Marching Band, January 1957 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Marching: For Marching Bands, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - The Marching Band, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Marching With Music; Teacher’s Manual; Bird, George “Red”, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Michigan State University Spartans Window Decal (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Modern Harmonic Technique; Vol. II, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Multi Percussion Cadences; Set 6 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Music in Your Schools (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - The Music of Henry Filmore and Will Huff, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - National Band Association; Vol. 29, No. 2, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - National Band Association; Vol. 29, No. 4, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - National Band Association; Vol. 29, No. 3, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - National Band Association; Vol. 30, No. 2, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - NBA Journal; Volume XXX, No. 3, May 1990 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - NBA Selective Music List, undated (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Neighborhoods: A Magazine for Jacksonville’s Communities; Vol. 2, Issue 2, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - New Sounds in Percussion 10-1, undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - New Sounds in Percussion 10-2, undated (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - New Sounds in Percussion 10-3, undated (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Panorama USA, undated (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - The Percussion, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Percussion Book; No Cover, title unknown; with copies (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Performing Corps-Style Music, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Pop Choral Showcase, undated (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Practical Band Instrument Repair Manual, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Practical Guide for the Working Drummer, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Practical Orchestration, 1929 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Precision Drumming, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Prelude to Jazz, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Premier Sticktips; Percussion Education Series (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Progressive Steps to Syncopation for the Modern Drummer, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - The Ramsay Lewis Songbook, undated (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Rhapsody for Solo Clarinet and Band, undated (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - The Reg Owen Arranging Method, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - Robert Shaw Choral Series, undated (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - The Rodgers and Hart Songbook, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - Row-Loff Productions, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Scoring Examples for Contemporary Marching Percussion (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Solo Guide; Book One, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Song Work II; Singing from Sound to Symbol, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Songs for Devils, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Songs for Organ with the Painter System, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Soundpower, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Soundpower, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Spectacular Bandbook, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - The Spirit of ’76 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Staggered Block Drill Movements; Casavant, A.R., 1961 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Stick Central, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Street Parade Drills; Casavant, A.R., 1959 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Student’s Guide to Dance and Stage Drumming (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - The Sweetheart of Sigma Chi; 28th Edition, 1927 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Teaching Band Instruments to Beginners, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Tenor – Scotch and Scotch Bass Drum, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Texas Bandmasters Association; 31st Annual New Music-Marching Clinic, July 30-August 2, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Timbrels Forward, undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Tricks of the Trade, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Trombone Ensemble; Equale No. 2, undated (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Twas the Night Before Christmas; for four part mixed voices (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - The University of Texas Longhorn Band; Texas vs. Houston Program, November 5, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - We’re the F.F.A, undated (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Who’s Who Among Students in American Universities and Colleges, 1949-1950 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Who’s Who in the Southwest, 1978-1979 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Ziggy, undated (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Music Education Sourcebook, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Music in American Schools, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- Awards
  This series consists of awards given to Dr. William C. Moffit. It is arranged alphabetically and chronologically, and contains 9 boxes. Oversized awards may be found in OVS Boxes 52-58.
  - Astroworld Marching Band Festival; William C. Moffit Festival Judge, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Beta Sigma (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - City of Galveston, Texas, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Freedom’s Foundation at Valley Forge, undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Cougar Cager Club, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Gamma Pi; Bill Moffit (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Gamma Pi; Jeannette Moffit (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - GCC Marching Band, undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Michigan State University; M.S.U. Men’s Club, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - “Music Makes Me Healthy” Mallwalker Program, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - National Cougar Club; Friend of the University of Houston Award for Special Achievement, undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Beta Phi, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Baldwin Wallace College, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Florence State College, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Honorary Spartan Spirit Director, 1964-1965 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Marching Symposium; East Tennessee State University, June 1967 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Kappa Kappa Psi, undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Kappa Kappa Psi, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Kappa Kappa Psi, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Kappa Kappa Psi, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Kappa Kappa Psi, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Kappa Kappa Psi, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Outstanding Spirit Organization; Cougar Brass, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Otterbein College, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Otterbein College, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Otterbein College, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Clear Lake Chamber of Commerce Christmas Boat Lane; Houseboat Special Award, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Clear Lake Chamber of Commerce, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Clear Lake Chamber of Commerce, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Denison University; Bloom-Carroll High School Band; Ohio, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - National Music Festival, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - The Cougar Marching Band, January 1, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Fall, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Indiana State Senate (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Region XIX Honor Band, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Cougar Band, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - The Nineteen Hundred and Eighty Merit Award (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Rhythm Roulette; Certificate of Appreciation, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Texas Bandmasters Association; President, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - McCltcheon High School; Honorary Directors; Dr. William C. and Jeannette Moffit, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Crawfordsville, Indiana, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Crawfordsville, Indiana, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Newcomer of the Year; Jeannette Moffit, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Marquis Who’s Who Publication Board; 19th Edition, 1984-1985 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Marques Who’s Who Publication Board; 20th Edition, 1986-1987 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Purdue University, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Lafayette Lions Club; Purdue, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Tau Beta Sigma, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Tau Beta Sigma, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Westerville American Revolution Bicentennial Commission; Certificate of Appreciation, November 20 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Artist’s Sketch of Bill Moffit (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - General Unframed Band Photographs (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - General Unframed Band Photographs (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Photographs; general (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Moffit Self-Framed Photographs (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Band Framed Photographs (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Band Configuration Patterns; Framed Photographs (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - All-America Gold Committee, undated (Ovs box 52, Item 1)